AHMED LOURO PROVEDO

Senior Software Developer

CONTACT

MOBILE:

+569 882-32-302

LINKEDIN PROFILE:

www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-louro-provedo-23a66911a

E-MAIL ahmedlouro@gmail.com

ABSTRACT

Accomplished Enterprise Senior Software Engineer, capable of making significant changes in short time span and overpressured, enjoy playing around with Backend Techs. Big challenges and on-going improvement processes are my professional "must-stand-for" goals. High analytic and learning skills, with a natural leadership and very good communication and teamwork expertises.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Software Developer at Tanner Corp (Chile, December 2020 – Present).
- Senior Software Developer at Gosocket Corporation (Chile, May 2017 – November 2020).
- Software Development Team Lead at Laboratorios AICA (Cuba, September 2012 - April 2017).
- Business Logic Developer at UCID (Cuba, September 2010
 August 2012).

EDUCATION

• Software Developer Engineer, Universidad Tecnológica de La Habana José Antonio Echeverría (Cuba, 2010).

CERTIFICATIONS AND EVENTS

- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (Chile, 2020).
- Software Logical Support Registration Certificate, No.1127793431. DIRECCION NACIONAL DE DERECHO DE AUTOR, Colombia. SVGET Project (Colombia, 2020).
- AZURE Bootcamp Chile Event (Chile, 2018).
- IELTS Degree, University of Cambridge (UK, 2016).

SKILLS

- 10+ years' experience as a Software Developer.
- 5+ years' experience in Azure Cloud and Microsoft Visual Studio C# Senior Developer.
- Experience with agile development methodologies.
- Experience with debugging, performance profiling and optimization.
- Comprehensive understanding of object-oriented and service-oriented application development techniques and theories.
- Internally motivated, able to work proficiently both independently and in a team environment.
- Strong communication skills with both internal team members and external business stakeholders.
- Strong initiative to find ways to improve solutions, systems, and processes.

LANGUAGE

Spanish: NativeEnglish: Advanced